[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1010_0101_seadog_brew",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1010_0101_seadog_brew_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1010_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1010_0101_seadog_brew_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1010_0101_seadog_brew_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1010_0101_seadog_brew_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1010_0101_seadog_brew_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1010_0101_seadog_brew_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1010_0101_seadog_brew_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1010_0101_seadog_brew_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1010_0102_eternal_mixes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1010_0102_eternal_mixes_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1010_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1010_0102_eternal_mixes_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1010_0102_eternal_mixes_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1010_0102_eternal_mixes_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1010_0102_eternal_mixes_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1010_0102_eternal_mixes_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1010_0102_eternal_mixes_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1010_0102_eternal_mixes_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0101_ancient_wonders",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0101_ancient_wonders_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1002_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0101_ancient_wonders_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1002_0101_ancient_wonders_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0101_ancient_wonders_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0101_ancient_wonders_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0101_ancient_wonders_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0101_ancient_wonders_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0101_ancient_wonders_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0102_aeternum_triangle",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1002_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_06",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0102_aeternum_triangle_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0103_skull_fort",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0103_skull_fort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1002_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0103_skull_fort_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1002_0103_skull_fort_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0103_skull_fort_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0103_skull_fort_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0103_skull_fort_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0103_skull_fort_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0103_skull_fort_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0101_explosive_prospecting",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1004_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1004_0101_explosive_prospecting_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0102_missing_features",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0102_missing_features_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1004_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0102_missing_features_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1004_0102_missing_features_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0102_missing_features_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1004_0102_missing_features_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1004_0102_missing_features_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1004_0102_missing_features_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1004_0102_missing_features_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1005_0101_lightning_bottle",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1005_0101_lightning_bottle_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1005_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1005_0101_lightning_bottle_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1005_0101_lightning_bottle_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1005_0101_lightning_bottle_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1005_0101_lightning_bottle_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1005_0101_lightning_bottle_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1005_0101_lightning_bottle_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1005_0101_lightning_bottle_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1005_0102_lightning_test",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1005_0102_lightning_test_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1005_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1005_0102_lightning_test_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1005_0102_lightning_test_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1005_0102_lightning_test_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1005_0102_lightning_test_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1005_0102_lightning_test_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1005_0102_lightning_test_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1005_0102_lightning_test_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1003_0101_watcher_coin",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1003_0101_watcher_coin_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1003_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1003_0101_watcher_coin_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1003_0101_watcher_coin_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1003_0101_watcher_coin_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1003_0101_watcher_coin_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1003_0101_watcher_coin_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1003_0101_watcher_coin_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1003_0101_watcher_coin_complete_availaible_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc4"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1001_0101_heads_tails",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1001_0101_heads_tails_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1001_0101_heads_tails_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1001_0101_heads_tails_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1001_0101_heads_tails_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1001_0101_heads_tails_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1001_0101_heads_tails_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1001_0101_heads_tails_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1001_0101_heads_tails_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "CutlassKeysArc4"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1001_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_13",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1001_0101a_heads_tails_watcher_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1003_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_12",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1001_0101b_heads_tails_survivalist_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1030_0201_animalinstincts",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1030_0201_animalinstincts_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1030_Tamer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_15",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1030_0201_animalinstincts_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1030_0201_animalinstincts_title",
        "Description": "@1030_0201_animalinstincts_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1030_0201_animalinstincts_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1030_0201_animalinstincts_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1030_0201_animalinstincts_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1030_0201_animalinstincts_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1030_0202_snaggletooth",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1030_0202_snaggletooth_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1030_Tamer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_15",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1030_0202_snaggletooth_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1030_0202_snaggletooth_title",
        "Description": "@1030_0202_snaggletooth_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1030_0202_snaggletooth_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1030_0202_snaggletooth_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1030_0202_snaggletooth_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1030_0202_snaggletooth_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1030_0203_catnipping",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1030_0203_catnipping_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1030_Tamer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_16",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1030_0203_catnipping_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1030_0203_catnipping_title",
        "Description": "@1030_0203_catnipping_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1030_0203_catnipping_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1030_0203_catnipping_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1030_0203_catnipping_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1030_0203_catnipping_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1030_Tamer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_17",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_title",
        "Description": "@1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1030_0204_tamingthelionhearted_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1030_0205_perfectcompanion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1030_0205_perfectcompanion_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1030_Tamer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_18",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1030_0205_perfectcompanion_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1030_0205_perfectcompanion_title",
        "Description": "@1030_0205_perfectcompanion_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1030_0205_perfectcompanion_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1030_0205_perfectcompanion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1030_0205_perfectcompanion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1030_0205_perfectcompanion_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1031_0201_adisturbingsilence",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1031_SwampWalker",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_20",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_title",
        "Description": "@1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1031_0201_adisturbingsilence_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1031_0202_trackingbyteeth",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1031_SwampWalker",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_20",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_title",
        "Description": "@1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1031_0202_trackingbyteeth_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1031_0203_heartofthemarsh",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1031_SwampWalker",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_21",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_title",
        "Description": "@1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1031_0203_heartofthemarsh_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 26,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1032_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_23",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_title",
        "Description": "@1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1032_0201_onewhotolledthebells_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1032_0202_bridgetonowhere",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1032_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_23",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_title",
        "Description": "@1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1032_0202_bridgetonowhere_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1032_0203_onebridgetoofar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1032_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_24",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_title",
        "Description": "@1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1032_0203_onebridgetoofar_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1032_0204_burningbridges",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1032_0204_burningbridges_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1032_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_25",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1032_0204_burningbridges_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1032_0204_burningbridges_title",
        "Description": "@1032_0204_burningbridges_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1032_0204_burningbridges_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1032_0204_burningbridges_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1032_0204_burningbridges_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1032_0204_burningbridges_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1033_0201_treasureisland",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1033_0201_treasureisland_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1033_TreasureHunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_27",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1033_0201_treasureisland_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1033_0201_treasureisland_title",
        "Description": "@1033_0201_treasureisland_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1033_0201_treasureisland_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1033_0201_treasureisland_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1033_0201_treasureisland_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1033_0201_treasureisland_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1033_TreasureHunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_27",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_title",
        "Description": "@1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1033_0202_trailofthemisanthrope_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1034_0201_motherocean",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1034_0201_motherocean_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1034_Navigator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_29",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1034_0201_motherocean_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1034_0201_motherocean_title",
        "Description": "@1034_0201_motherocean_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1034_0201_motherocean_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1034_0201_motherocean_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1034_0201_motherocean_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1034_0201_motherocean_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1034_0202_seadreams",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1034_0202_seadreams_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1034_Navigator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_29",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1034_0202_seadreams_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1034_0202_seadreams_title",
        "Description": "@1034_0202_seadreams_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1034_0202_seadreams_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1034_0202_seadreams_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1034_0202_seadreams_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1034_0202_seadreams_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1034_0203_hightide",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1034_0203_hightide_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1034_Navigator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_31",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_30",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1034_0203_hightide_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1034_0203_hightide_title",
        "Description": "@1034_0203_hightide_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1034_0203_hightide_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1034_0203_hightide_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1034_0203_hightide_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1034_0203_hightide_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1035_0201_cookiecrumbles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_container_d_00",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1035_Chef",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_32",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_title",
        "Description": "@1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1035_0201_cookiecrumbles_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1002_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_09",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_01_Boots",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0104_01_Boots_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_Boots",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_01_Boots_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_01_Boots_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_01_Boots_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_01_Boots_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_01_Boots_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_01_Boots_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_01_Boots_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_02_Coat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0104_02_Coat_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_Coat",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_02_Coat_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_02_Coat_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_02_Coat_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_02_Coat_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_02_Coat_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_02_Coat_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_02_Coat_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_03_Pants",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0104_03_Pants_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_Pants",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_03_Pants_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_03_Pants_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_03_Pants_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_03_Pants_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_03_Pants_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_03_Pants_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_03_Pants_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_04_Gloves",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0104_04_Gloves_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_Gloves",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_04_Gloves_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_04_Gloves_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_04_Gloves_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_04_Gloves_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_04_Gloves_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_04_Gloves_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_04_Gloves_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_05_Hat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1002_0104_05_Hat_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_Hat",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_05_Hat_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_05_Hat_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_05_Hat_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_05_Hat_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_05_Hat_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_05_Hat_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_05_Hat_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1004_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "10_Quest_09",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_QuenchingOil_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0103_QuenchingOil_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_QuenchingOil_Quest_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1004_0103_QuenchingOil_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0103_QuenchingOil_Quest_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_HiltLeather_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0103_HiltLeather_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_HiltLeather_Quest_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1004_0103_HiltLeather_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0103_HiltLeather_Quest_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_Grindstone_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0103_Grindstone_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_Grindstone_Quest_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1004_0103_Grindstone_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0103_Grindstone_Quest_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_CaptainsBlade_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1004_0103_CaptainsBlade_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_CaptainsBlade_Quest_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1004_0103_CaptainsBlade_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0103_CaptainsBlade_Quest_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Spy_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Spy_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Poach_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Poach_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Spy_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Spy_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Poach_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Poach_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1001_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1001_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1002_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1002_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1003_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1003_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1004_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1004_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1005_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1005_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1006_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1006_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1007_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1007_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1008_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1008_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1009_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1009_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1010_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1010_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1001_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1001_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1002_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1002_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1003_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1003_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1004_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1004_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1005_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1005_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1006_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1006_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1007_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1007_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1008_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1008_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1009_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1009_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1010_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1010_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1001_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1001_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1002_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1002_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1003_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1003_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1004_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1004_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1005_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1005_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1006_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1006_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1007_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1007_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1008_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1008_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1009_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1009_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1010_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1010_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1061_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1061_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1062_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1062_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1063_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1063_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1064_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1064_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1065_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1065_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1066_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1066_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1067_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1067_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1068_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1068_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1069_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1069_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1070_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1070_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1061_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1061_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1062_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1062_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1063_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1063_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1064_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1064_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1065_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1065_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1066_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1066_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1067_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1067_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1068_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1068_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1069_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1069_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1070_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1070_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1061_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1061_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1062_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1062_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1063_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1063_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1064_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1064_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1065_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1065_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1066_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1066_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1067_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1067_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1068_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1068_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1069_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1069_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1070_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1070_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_10_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_10_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_10_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_10_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]